Miller, Frank, Papers /4311
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Frank Miller Papers
1870-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Miller, Frank
/4311
5 cubic feet
5 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
ILR lecture notes, draft of Miller's book on the history of personnel, notes and drafts of the book ILR at 50.
8491264
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 06, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Frank B. Miller joined the ILR School faculty in 1954 as an assistant professor after completing his Ph.D. there and undergraduate studies in psychology at Reed College. He became associate professor in 1960 and professor in 1966.
During his 31 years as a faculty member, Miller taught courses on a range of subjects, including complex organizations; small groups in industrial organizations; and applied human relations. He also designed the first course on women in the workplace at the ILR School and co-taught it with colleague Alice Cook, a world-renowned expert on issues faced by working women. In addition, Miller chaired the organizational behavior department for several years (1967-69) and served two terms as director of the school's Office of Resident Instruction (1962-67).
As a visiting professor at the University of Istanbul in 1960-61, Miller gave lectures that were translated into Turkish and became a textbook for personnel studies courses there. He also contributed chapters to books on industrial sociology and worker incentives and was a fellow of the American Sociological Society and the Society of Applied Anthropology.
Although he attained emeritus status in 1985, Miller continued teaching part time at Cornell and Bernard Baruch College in New York City for another 10 years.
Scope and Contents
Consists of research, class, and lecture notes for ILR 366: Women at Work. These files contain extensive notes on gender difference, work-life balance, comparable pay, and other workplace gender issues. Also notes on ILR 9765: Special Topics in Human Resource Management: Women in Work Organizations. Includes correspondence and drafts of The Historical Sources of Personnel Work, an Annotated Bibliography of Developments to 1923 and "The Coffee Table Book", The ILR School at Fifty.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4210: Frank B. Miller Files /4259: Frank B. Miller Corning Glass files /4308m: Frank Miller ILR School Poetry /4331: Frank B. Miller Collections
Miller, Frank
8491264
- Work is Man's Greatest Function (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 366 Final Exam and Outline-Format (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Psychology Today, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The Brain: His and Hers (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Sociological Quarterly. Article by Hunt, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Women Labor Force Participation Transparencies. ILR 9765 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Quest. Article by Durden-Smith, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Industrial Relations Research Assoc., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Quest. Jo Durden-Smith, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- McGlone. Synopsis. Men/Women Brain Bilateral Symmetry (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Men/Women Brain. Kimura (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Japanese Brain (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Transparencies 366 Seg. One (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Cheryl Rink ILR 366 Magazines (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Science. Article by Sibatani, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Conflicts Between Work and Family Life. Peck, Staires, Lang. Seg. IV (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Science. Article by Sibatani, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Math and Sex. ILR Baruch (Box 1, Folder 18)
- The American Workforce by Sex and Occupation. The Leading 10 Occupations of Women Workers, 1870-1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Sex and Mathematics. Alice T. Schafer. Science, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Scope and Contents
  January 1981
- Culture and Personality. Wallace. Norms (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Women in the Labor Force, Selected Years, 1900-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- N.Y. Times, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Table 1-3: Labor Force Participation Rates of Women and Men, Annual Averages, 1950-1981 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Sociological Quarterly. Article by Hunt, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- ILR 366. 1st Day Exercise (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Comparison of Four-Person Homemaker and Working-Wife Families, Sample, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Descriptive Stat. Handouts on Women Early in Course (Box 1, Folder 28)
- ILR 366. Fall 1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Labor Force Participation over a Working Life of Cohorts of Women Born in Selected Time Intervals, 1886-1955 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Comparison of Four-Person Homemaker and Working-Wife Families, Sample, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Employment of Women in Select Occupations, 1950-1979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Transparencies (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Aberle. The Functional Prerequisites of a Society (Box 1, Folder 34)
- AP Report. Cornell Sun, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  March 14, 1983
- Holland. Making Vocational Choices (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Life Cycle Considerations (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Court to TIAA. Chronicle Higher Education, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  October 16, 1982
- TIAA Case Equal Pension Benefits for Women (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Pension Recipients, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Negative Appeals Court. TIAA Benefits for Women (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Health Insurance. CU Statutory (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Chronicle (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Social Security and Women. US Chamber of Commerce (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Social Security Payout Formula. Fairness Questions (Box 1, Folder 45)
- 10th Week Handouts (Box 1, Folder 46)
- International Income Inequality (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Cornell Colleges' Employee Benefits (Box 1, Folder 48)
- 366 Women's Share of Bachelor Degrees (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Vetter. Science PhD's Women Pessimistic Transparency Slides, 1965-1985 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Engr. Sci. Women Parrish (Optimistic) (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Sokoloff on Professions (Box 1, Folder 52)
- 1st Day Handout ILR 366. Levy (Box 1, Folder 53)
- AT&T Consent Degree (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Assorted Women Handouts (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Industrial Relations Research Assoc., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Personnel Journal. Jones, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Sociological Quarterly. Article by Hunt, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Is There a Superior Sex? Health and Sex (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Girl Talk Boy Talk, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  January - February
- Monthly Labor Review. Article by Kamerman, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Assorted Women Course Materials (Box 1, Folder 62)
- ILR 366 Transparencies. Social Policy (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Annals of Science. A Silent Childhood, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Xerox. Sales Representatives Material (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Benefit Costs. GM News Item (Box 1, Folder 66)
- More Women Brain. Psychology Today (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Child Care Program Begun to Aid, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 68)
- EEOC, Goodyear Reach $5 Million, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Seventh Circuit Affirms Sears', 1988 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Journal of Social Issues. Farley, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Journal of Social Issues. Graham et al., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Miller, 366. Final Exam (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Miller, 366. Midterm Exam (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Miller, 366. Midterm Exam (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Journal of Vocational Behavior, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Annual Income by Age, for Male and Female High School and College Graduates (Box 1, Folder 77)
- One More Time: What is the Nature of the Earnings Gap?, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Equal Employment for Women (Box 1, Folder 79)
- USA Family Configurations, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Journal of Vocational Behavior, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Monthly Labor Review. Article by Kamerman, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- N.Y. Times Magazine, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Sex Differences in the Entry into Marriage, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Lloyd. Sex Discrimination and the Division of Labor (Box 1, Folder 85)
- US Bureau of Employment Security (Box 1, Folder 86)
- US Bureau of Employment Security (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Journal of Vocational Behavior, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Women (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Cornell University Workbook (Box 1, Folder 90)
- A Women's Guide to Apprenticeship, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Non-Traditional OCC's, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Effects of Education and Occupational Training on the Wages of Mature Women, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- The Coal Employment Project, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 94)
- The CRIAW Papers (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Accommodating the Spectrum of Individual Abilities, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Selection Interview (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Career Guide for Women in Science (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Economic Consequences of Marital Disruption (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Books (Box 1, Folder 100)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 101)
- Sex Roles. Article by Cheatham, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Review. Article by Ferber and Green, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Industrial and Labor Relations Review. Article by Ferber and Green, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Change. Article by Astin and Snyder, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Monthly Labor Review. Article by Kamerman, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Psychology Today. Article by Goleman, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Quest. Article by Durden-Smith, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Science. Article by Sibatani, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Miller, 366, Final Exam (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Seventh Circuit Affirms Sears', 1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Miller, 366. Midterm Exam (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Journal of Social Issues. Farley, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Journal of Vocational Behavior. Fassinger, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Journal of Social Issues. Graham, et al., 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Personnel Journal. Jones, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Industrial Relations Research Assoc., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Journal of Vocational Behavior. O'Hare and Beutell, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Journal of Vocational Behavior. Walker, et al., 1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Business Affairs. Office - Sex Complications (Box 2, Folder 19)
- International Comparisons. Projections (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Human Resource Executive Handouts, Women-Relevant (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Degree Completion by Women and Minorities Handout (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Women Lawyers. Mommy Track Relevant, 1960-1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Flexible Benefits. Cafeteria (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Top 50 Personnel Execs, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Higher Education Guidelines Executive Order 11246 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Geographic Constraints on Women's Careers in Academia. Marwell, Rosenfeld, Spilerman (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Women Lawyers (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Experts Say Bias Persists (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Van Alstyne. Equality for Individuals? Equality for Groups? (Box 2, Folder 31)
- ILR 366 Seg. Four. Teenage Parents (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Dual-Career Couples Working at Being Equal. The Oregonian (Box 2, Folder 33)
- The Second Shift (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Battle over Maternity Leave. N.Y. Times, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  July 22, 1984
- Occupational Distribution of Experienced Black Women Workers, 1950-1980 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Special Report: Overhauling Welfare in Wisconsin, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Women, Work, and Health Insurance. National Commission on Working Women (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Inequality of Pay I (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Income Inequality Measures II (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Leonard on Affirmative Action II (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Constitutional/Practical Questions. Government Intervention in Labor Management (Box 2, Folder 42)
- International Comparison Material. ILR (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Wife Employment Husband Depression (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Nonfamily Living and the Erosion of Traditional Family Orientations Among Young Adults, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- NLS Update Handout, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  Winter 1988
- Social Policy Strategies (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Personal Strategies Self-Help (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Strategies for Help Transparencies (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Occupation-Specific Studies: Women Workers (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Non-Traditional Careers (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Sex Comparisons, Work Relevance? 366 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Changes in the Sex Composition of US Occupations, 1960-1981 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Transition to Non-Traditional Occupations (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Transparencies. Lawyers, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Non-Traditional Women Jobs (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Women in Labor Force (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Science Reprints. Aronson (Box 2, Folder 58)
- ILR 366 Reserve (Box 2, Folder 59)
- IV General Role Strain Stuff (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Segment Four (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Families and Jobs. ILR 366 Seg. Four (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Careers and Paychecks. Newspaper Article (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Couple's Suicide Over Bride Price Shocks Turks (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Jobs or Babies? Japan's Women Assay Priorities (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Marital Stability: Women Work (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Marriage (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Wage and Salary Transparencies. Benefit (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Comparable Worth and Income Inequality (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Brookings Review. Burtless, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- The Ford Foundation Letter, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Average Salary Offer Bachelor Degree by Sex and Specialty, 1876 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- 366 Job Evaluation Transparencies. Seg. Five (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Equal Pay for Women. Edit. Pettman. Seg. 5 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- B. Gerhart. Gender Difference. Seg. Five Handout (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Milkovich I+II. Earnings Gap (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Cornell Makes News re. Women (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Feminization of Poverty. Income Shares by 5ths (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Text of Court Decision Equalizing TIAA. Benefits for Men, Women, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Poverty. Social Security Pension Protection (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Why Bring Sex into Pensions (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Ms. Christina Engfelot. Sweden. Women/ Social Policies (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Federal Careers Civilian and Military (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Working Parents (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Degrees in Higher Education, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 85)
- Minorities and Women in the World of Work (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Women in Science (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Rosabeth Moss Kanter Article. Applications Method for Change (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Civil Rights Update, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Intent vs. Effects. N.Y. Times Article Handout (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Social Security and Women, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Vladeck. The Kryiazi Case Reviewed (Box 2, Folder 92)
- Affirmative Action Labor Force Availability (Box 2, Folder 93)
- EEOC, Goodyear Reach $5 Million, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 94)
- Daily Labor Report, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Segment Seven Handouts (Box 2, Folder 96)
- Daily Labor Report, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Leonard. Affirmative Action I (Box 2, Folder 98)
- EEOC's Definition of Illegal Sexual Harassment (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Seg. Six (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Careers and Paychecks. USA Today, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  May 29, 1984
- West Coast Localities. N.Y. Times, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  Sunday, May 1, 1988
- Dependent Care in the 1990s, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 103)
- Sociological Quarterly. Article by Hunt, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 104)
- Miscellaneous folder 1 (Box 2, Folder 105)
- Miscellaneous folder 2 (Box 2, Folder 106)
- Women at Work Summer School, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- U. N. Mexico Women Conference (Box 3, Folder 2)
- The Problem of Equal Pay for Equal Work. ILR 366 Seg. I (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Feshback. USSR Demographic Transparencies (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Child Policy. Wilson Quar., 1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Summary of Benefits. Cornell (Statutory) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Projected Change in Employment by Major Occupational Group, 1978-1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Shinar Perception Study. Outline of Study (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Comparable Math Scores by Nation and Sex (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Who is Really Better at Math? Time, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  March 1982
- Sex and Mathematics. Science, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Women vs. Men. Who Have Best Brains? Oregonian, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  November 18, 1984
- History Handouts 366 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  June 6
- Review. Deevey Pop. Curves (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Women/Men in Labor Force Tables, 1950-1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Deevey. Pop. Density Estimates (Box 3, Folder 16)
- ILR 151 Population Densities. Pictograph, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Spring 1987
- Population Curve. ILR 151 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Occupational Winners and Losers 1972-1980. MLReview, Carol Leon, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  June 1982
- Chart 1-1: The Gap Between the Participation Rates of Women and Men (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Recent Women LFPR Changes Curve (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Levy Handout (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Reinterpreting the History of Women (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Women Job Changes, 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Is There a Superior Sex? Durden (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Weintraub. On Brain (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Recent Change in Women LFPR Tables, 1955-1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- ILR 366 Segment I Handouts (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Women at Work - ILR Card Catalog/ Bibliographies on Women Studies (Box 3, Folder 29)
- M. Major (Box 3, Folder 30)
- ILR Library. Info Sources. Occupations. ILR 366 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Women Workers Win One in New York. Seg. VII (Box 3, Folder 32)
- 366 Course Format, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Job Description Assignment (Box 3, Folder 34)
- ILR 9765 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Mommy Track. BNA etc. Lecture CU. Women at Work, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  Spring 1983
- Ph. D. Comparisons by Sex (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Chris S. (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Departmental History (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Chapter Three: Photographs (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Annual Dept. Reports Hum. Res. Stud. & Predecessors (Box 3, Folder 41)
- The Take-Off Period Personnel and Human Resource Studies, 1979-1986 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Dept. History. Miscellaneous Addit. Copies of Segments (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Coffee Table Book Draft folder 1 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Coffee Table Book Draft folder 2 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- 9765 Term Papers, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- ILR 9765. Alicia Ford (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Health Careers Evaluation Faculty, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Robert Metchick. Letter of Rec., 1991 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  Spring 1991
- Elizabeth Burns (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Lisa Cosimi (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Anthony Loizides (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Med School Candidates, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Anjali Sadarangani (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Health Career Interviews (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Health Careers Evaluations, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- David Sam (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Sarah Kohn (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Stephanie Swan (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Confidential. Beth Ehrhardt. Med School Applicant, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  Envelope
- Occupational Distrib. Women. Baruch. ILR (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Day Care: A National Crisis, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Addressing Sexual Harassment at Work, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Absenteeism, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Women and the Glass Ceiling, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Women's Roles in Organization and Their Impact on Child Care Programs, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Hawthorne. Phase Two (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Relay Assembly Follow-up 4 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Recapitulating Hawthorne 151 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Intro Hawthorne Slide 1 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Hawthorne Relay Assembly Test Room 2 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Definitions. Incent. Motive (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Harwood Mfg. 1 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Harwood Mfg. 2 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Harwood Mfg. 3 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Seashore Study (Box 3, Folder 76)
- A. H. Leighton. Morale (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Miller. Sample Prelim (Box 3, Folder 78)
- ILR 151 Final Exam, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- McGregor's Theory and Assumptions (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Predictors. Criteria Measures (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Brockway Machinery Company (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Warmup Interview Exercises (Box 3, Folder 83)
- 151 Week 1+2 Transparencies and Notes (Box 3, Folder 84)
- The Ideal Type (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Toynbee. Challenge and Response (Box 3, Folder 86)
- Riesman. Character Types (Box 3, Folder 87)
- Maslow's Hierarchy (Box 3, Folder 88)
- Herz Berg. Two-Factors (Box 3, Folder 89)
- Motivators Handout (Box 3, Folder 90)
- Hygiene Factors Handout (Box 3, Folder 91)
- McGregor. Theory X/ Theory Y (Box 3, Folder 92)
- Simple (F. Miller) Organization Chart (Box 3, Folder 93)
- 3 Types of Appraisal Interview. Maier (Box 3, Folder 94)
- Coaching. 3-Way Stake (Box 3, Folder 95)
- G. E. Appraisal Study (Box 3, Folder 96)
- Rationality and Rating Strategies (Controlling the Rater (Box 3, Folder 97)
- N. A. Labor History Landscape (Box 3, Folder 98)
- Interview with Margie (Box 3, Folder 99)
- The Girl Who Couldn't Take Criticism (Box 3, Folder 100)
- Walt Rogers (Box 3, Folder 101)
- Gillen Radio Corporation (Box 3, Folder 102)
- Union-Management Jargon (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Game Theory and Collective Bargaining Strategic Outcomes (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Unfair Labor Practices (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Structure: US Labor Unions (Box 4, Folder 4)
- (Local) Grievance Procedure (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Plant-Level UN Management Relations (Box 4, Folder 6)
- AFSCME-CSEA Salaries. Officer and Sergeant (Box 4, Folder 7)
- CU Pay. '86 Faculty Salary and Compensation, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- CU Faculty Compensation (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Prof's Salaries and Benefits Compared by Institution and Rank (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Bosses. Subordinates' Interests for Career Development (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Freedom vs. Convenience (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Benefit Trends (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Catching Up with Mackay. 151 UN Management Relations (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Some Tips on Successful Monitoring (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Midterm and Final Exam (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Employers Unprepared for Pending Bill (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Social Security Equity (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Pension Handout Benefits (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Employment Growth in Temporary Help. Chart (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Outline. Reading List. ILR 9765, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- 366 Outline, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- ILR 9765. 1st Session Handouts (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Final Prelim ILR 9765, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- ILR/Baruch 9765 Admin, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Question 1 and Question 2 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- 2nd Session Handouts. ILR 9765 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- II Occupational Distribution Stats. (Box 4, Folder 28)
- 1st Round Transparencies. Session 2 9765 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Population Curves Handouts and Transparents (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Logarithmic Population Curve. F. Miller's Version (Box 4, Folder 31)
- The Brain: His and Hers, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Sociological Quarterly. Article by Hunt, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Women/Men Math Performance (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Sex Difference in Math: More Facts. Science, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  December 1983
- Minorities and Women in the World of Work (Box 4, Folder 36)
- ILR 366. Math and Sex: Are Girls Born With Less Ability? (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Session Three. Brain Notes and Transparencies (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Hunt. Sex Stratification and Male Biography (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Segment Two Transparencies (Box 4, Folder 40)
- ILR 366 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- I Women Labor Market Statistics. ILR 9765. LFPR's by Year (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Women Labor Force. ILR 9765 Handouts, 1870-1989 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Explanations (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Women's Issues (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Pre-Employment Inquiries. ILR 366 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- What do the Uniform Guidelines Include? (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Job Evaluation Handouts. ILR 9765 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Risks of an Industrial Society Handouts. Rationale (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Transparencies/Handouts Comp. Worth (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Manager's Guide to EEO. Table of Contents. ILR 151 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Explanations (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Transparencies, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  April 18, 1988